Why do you change the mask?
The previous one is good.
That one has been worn too many times.
It's not as good-looking as the previous one.
Put it on, let me see.
Jiang Yi,
I'll take a photo
of your early love.
What's wrong with you today?
You're on stage soon with a long face.
Aren't you afraid the audience will say you're being a diva?
We have masks.
Don't worry.
Captain,
can we do something new?
We've played this old song
so many times.
It's boring.
Play it 800 times
to earn money from 800 performances.
Can you play it 800 times first?
I'm begging you.
Besides,
your current level
is enough to perform old songs.
I'm tired of playing.
I don't want to play.
Jiang Yi, did I do something to you?
If you're going to be angry,
don't take it out on me.
If you're so good,
go on stage
and vent your anger.
Rock it out, okay?
I got it.
Let me guess.
Who dares to mess with you?
Li Haoyu?
He didn't appreciate your help?
I didn't give him the gift.
You've been preparing for so long.
Why didn't you give it to him?
Just...
the timing was not right.
The timing was off?
If you don't give it to him
when you win,
what if you lose?
Spit it out!
I think
your brother
is hard to get along with.
It's not his fault.
It's hard to merge
two families.
My uncle is nice to me,
but he forgot
Li Haoyu has feelings too.
It's our fault for not getting along.
I don't
know how to
be a good sister.
That's when...
What about your gift?
Find another chance to give it to him.
Who is it?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's continue preparing.
Hello everyone.
We are The Landlord's Cat.
I am Xiaohei.
Hello everyone.
I am Peiling.
Today, we bring you a song
The Train Passes Through Dawn.
It's because we didn't get along well with him.
I also
don't know how to
be a good sister.
Didn't you say you were not interested?
Why did you come first?
Since I'm here,
I'll just take a look.
I can't waste
Fu Binyan's kindness.
There are support props.
Do you want one?
Is there one for the guitarist?
I have a major discovery.
This guitarist with a black mask,
do you think
he looks like someone?
Like who?
Senior Jiang Yi.
Not at all.
We weren't wrong, then.
If it's really her,
I'll go home right now.
Help me with the light sticks.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Light sticks.
This spot looks good.
The position is high.
You can see the stage clearly.
Take good photos later.
Do you know?
Got it, Miss.
You must have said this a thousand times.
Alright.
Hurry up and listen to the music.
It will be a while
before the Over-the-Counter Drugs Band comes on stage.
I love you all.
It's so good.
The Landlord's Cat, I love you.
Pei Ling, I love you guys.
Sounds good, The Landlord's Cat, sounds good.
Sounds good.
Thank you.
Good evening, everyone.
We are the Over-the-Counter Drugs Band.
Over-the-Counter Drugs Band.
The first song, Towards the Light,
is dedicated to all those who chase the light
who chase the light together in the dark.
What's wrong?
Sorry.
There's a minor issue with the equipment.
Please wait a moment.
It seems to be a problem with the drum.
What?
The drum?
The pedal is broken.
What about the spare one?
We don't have a song with double pedal.
There's no spare one.
How about this?
Use the tom to replace the bass drum.
Play less fill.
Try it.
This is a formal performance.
The tone won't sound good.
What should we do?
Refund!
Gu Chenyang, help me hold this.
Everyone,
I'm sorry.
Li Haoyu,
please wait a moment, okay?
Refund, refund, refund.
Jiang Yi, Jiang Yi.
What's wrong?
The beater is broken, the bass drum can't be used.
Do you have a solution?
I can try.
Come up.
Okay.
Yu, go up.
Zhou.
Let him try.
You try.
If you trust me,
I can try.
Can you do it?
I will use my right hand instead of the pedal.
The original rhythm
and groove will not change.
Can you play the original?
I've heard it a few times.
Okay.
Thank you, our last-minute drummer.
Let's
Towards the Light again.
Fang Xu, I love you.
So cool.
Li Haoyu.
Thank you.
So cool.
Over-the-Counter Drugs.
Let's thank
our drummer again.
His name is
Li Haoyu.
Wait.
That was good.
I think it's good.
This one.
How is it?
Better?
Maybe it's because
I was too close to the speaker.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Here they come.
Sit here.
Hello.
I'm telling you,
that guitarist
is definitely Jiang Yi.
I can bet my head on it.
Your head
isn't always reliable.
Just tell us if it's her.
If she can get Li Haoyu
on stage to save the day,
it must be Jiang Yi.
What?
Really?
Let me see.
Here.
Don't mistake her for someone else.
The first two.
I didn't expect
Jiang Yi to have her own band.
No wonder she's
so good at playing the guitar.
Fu Binyan,
you knew she was Jiang Yi
before, didn't you?
How did you know?
Last month, at the Student Union,
at the Student Union last month.
That early?
Oh my god.
My idol
is actually my senior female student.
So,
when I told you Li Haoyu was upset
because of a family gathering,
you specially arranged
this team building
to let him see Jiang Yi's performance.
Not really.
It's just a coincidence.
That's you.
I'm impressed.
I'm really impressed.
Did you
arrange the drum to be broken?
That's why I said
you're unreliable.
Let's go.
What about Li Haoyu?
I think
we don't have to wait for him.
Let's go.
Go.
Sit.
Water.
Li Haoyu,
thank you for today.
You played the drum well.
Let's play together next time.
Sure.
And you,
your skills are getting better.
Of course.
Where are your hands?
What's the
relationship between you two?
What are you thinking?
This is my cousin, Fang Xu.
The aunt who complimented you
at the dinner
is his mom.
Then,
why didn't he come to dinner that day?
They thought I was at school.
My cousin
is a medical student at a prestigious university.
He wouldn't dare let his family know
about his band.
It's lucky he didn't come that day.
Otherwise, my dad
would have another reason
to scold me.
I'll go back
and do my homework.
You take care of him.
Who is he?
You.
Li Haoyu.
Jiang Yi.
You first.
This is for you.
Your prize for beating Sports Academy.
Headphones.
A new model.
I wanted to give it to you
when we were eating last time.
Thanks.
I'm glad you like it.
Okay.
I'll go first.
Wait.
Let's go back together.
I'll call a taxi.
Okay.
Let's go.
Li Haoyu.
Dad.
You're still up?
Put your backpack down.
What's wrong?
Stand straight.
You're back so late.
I just went to a party with my classmates.
Just a party today?
Nothing else?
You're a smart boy.
Do you want me to tell you
or do you want to tell me yourself?
I'm telling you.
A parent
from Yudong
called me today.
You mean the Yudong thing?
When the Yudong people came to school,
there was some
dispute.
And then?
Then...
Then they got physical.
I told you,
when you were a kid,
if there's a problem, talk it out.
If not, go to the teacher.
If still not, come to me.
Fighting is the sign of weakness.
You are my son, Li Jianye,
not some street thug.
But
they started it first.
So you hit them.
What if you encounter
similar problems in the future?
Will you always resort to violence?
What will happen to you in the future?
When you grow up,
the police will have enough evidence to arrest you.
You will have a criminal record.
Then,
you will be a social pariah.
Scum.
Dad, how can you say that to me?
What do you want me to say about you?
Look at what you are doing now.
You don't go home every day.
You hang out with these people.
You say you want to make a
name for yourself, and that's okay.
I've heard that
Yudong is the provincial champion.
What about you?
Listen,
I don't care
how well you play.
You just focus on
finishing your studies.
If not,
you'll drop out.
Stop playing.
Why are you saying that about them?
Because I'm your dad.
You're not my dad.
What did you say?
Even if they're not good,
when we're in trouble,
we face it together.
When I had a fever,
they took care of me.
Where were you?
I'm working hard
to make money for you.
Listen, Li Haoyu,
you will meet many classmates,
friends,
and buddies in your life.
But remember,
never compare them
to your dad.
Son,
in this world,
the one who gives you money
without asking for anything in return
is your true love.
You haven't answered my question.
What question?
Where were you when I had a fever?
When did you have a fever?
See,
you don't even know
when I had a fever.
Did you get hurt in the fight?
Now you're showing concern.
Cut down on the alcohol.